STANDARD FOR LIFE
Here is wise man Daniel at The SCOAN praying for the people in Jesus' name and restoring them back
to the original position, in which God Almighty had created them.
This man reacts violently, as light meets darkness through the touch of wise man Daniel.
Let's see how he was delivered in Jesus' name.
Come here!
Who are you? Speak!
I am the tiger.
What do you mean by saying you are a tiger?
I just need little.
If he can obey – no problem.
What have you done to him?
I have destroyed him.
He is nothing.
All he studied – nothing.
I wanted him to work and serve me with his money.
He said God called him.
Who is God?
Who is God that called him?
He then left me and served God.
I allowed him to flow and then after some time, I stepped in.
I destroyed all.
I laid accusations of so many things.
He is finished.
This one – he studied in Poland, in Marine Mechanical Engineering.
He worked in a shipping company here in this country.
He was a manager.
He resigned. Who asked him to resign?
I want him to work and use the money to serve me because I own him.
What have you done to his marriage and to his family?
Marriage?
I will destroy.
He can never have peace in marriage.
No friends.
He cannot have peace because he decided to serve a God that I don't know.
I want him to serve me.
I am a great lion.
I am the tiger...
Living where?
... from the deep sea of India.
Right form the day he was born in France, I came into the hospital and I owned him.
I followed him step to step.
I breastfed him and gave him everything.
How come, at the time to pay me, he turned to a God that I don’t know?
I allowed him.
Now - nothing.
He doesn't even have a house.
He stays in that church.
He is a pastor.
Let him pastor.
He will pastor and eat the dust unless he accepts to come back to me and serve me.
He must serve me.
What have you done to his ministry, as a pastor?
Ministry?
I swept everything, put in a container and sent it to the ocean.
Where in the ocean?
Right where I come from.
Everything about him, I parcelled it and sent it to the ocean, the deep ocean of India where I come from.
That is where he belongs; that is where his blessing is.
I am the god that gave him life.
Right from birth, I breastfed him.
I gave him everything, sent him to school and did everything for him.
Ask him.
He has a first degree in Marine Mechanical Engineering.
He is the best.
Ask him.
But nothing.
He can't go anywhere.
He is a pastor; he did well.
He has all the qualifications but cannot go anywhere unless he comes back to serve me.
How did you sweep everything about his ministry and parcel it to the ocean?
I allowed him to grow.
He was reigning.
When the time came, I caused problems in the church.
I laid allegations; all were false.
I made people to hate him without any cause.
What has happened to him ministry now?
Ministry?
There is no ministry.
You can go there and see.
Everything he has put there is just there.
Just him and the things he put there.
I called him.
He should come and serve me, not this God.
You said that when he was born, you possessed him right from the hospital.
Yes.
How did you go about it?
The nurse.
I came through the nurse.
The nurse was my agent.
I spat into his mouth and I possessed him.
Everybody loved him because I transferred myself.
Yes, that was like this.
He’s going to be a rich and successful man if only he decides to come back to me.
I own everything.
I will give him; he doesn't need to struggle.
He’s struggling, going left and right.
What have you done to his marriage?
Marriage.
No marriage.
Where is the marriage?
I spoiled everything.
How did you spoil his marriage?
Life is zero.
Life about marriage is zero.
What do you mean by that?
Do you know what is zero?
What?
When something is zero, it means it’s nothing.
It has no meaning.
You know, he belongs to me.
He doesn't belong to any woman.
I am the only person that owns him.
He will marry me, he will serve me and I will give him everything.
Madam, how are you?
I'm fine.
Who is he to you?
He's my husband.
Husband?
She said you are her husband.
No.
What do you meant by, 'no'?
I said anything about marriage is zero.
He has to marry me.
I am the only person he will marry and succeed.
Who is he to you?
He's my husband.
You mean that you came with him?
Yes, we came together.
She said she came with you.
I came here alone.
Since 4pm, I was here.
You know, I supervise the whole place.
I wanted to hide myself.
I just wanted to see if actually there is power here as they said.
I came alone.
So, you came to survey if actually there is power here?
I came to see if actually there is power.
Yes, that is what I came to see.
What did you now observe?
Because this one has tried deliverance, to get out of my hand, but still no way.
Wherever he goes, I just go there; I sit down and cross my legs.
I also came here to try to see if he can be delivered.
Let me see the power that is here.
So, I followed him.
I was here monitoring him.
What is happening to you now?
I don't know.
You asked me to speak and I spoke.
What do you have to say about what your husband is saying?
He always tells me that he dreams of a fat woman who says her name is tiger.
Everytime we fight, he says it’s me who has the problem and I need deliverance.
He always says that you are the one that needs deliverance?
Yes.
He says that you are the cause of the problem in the house?
What are you seeing now?
I see that it's him.
It's him that needs what?
Who was causing all the problems.
Don't worry. He will be delivered.
Right now, it is time you allow peace to reign in this temple.
It is time to quit the covenant.
Can you deliver him?
Do you know where you are?
You can't deliver this one.
This one from birth...
Listen to me.
Do you know where you are?
Here?
Yes.
Where is this place?
I told you that I came to see if actually there is power.
OK.
Come out!
All over your body, fire!
Out, in Jesus' name!
Your back on the floor!
Thank You, Lord.
You are delivered. Rise up.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
What happened to you, sir?
Come, sir.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
How are you, sir?
I'm fine.
What happened to you?
Why were you sitting there?
I don't know.
I think I stood there.
How did you find yourself on the floor?
I don't know.
I just saw myself on the floor there.
OK.
Do you remember what you just said now?
No.
Can I remind you?
OK.
You said you were the tiger.
My name is Pastor Ernest.
I am not a tiger.
You are not a tiger?
You also said that you are a lion.
Lion? I don't have a beast's face; I am a human being.
You don't have a beast's face?
You said you reside in the Red Sea in the Indian Ocean.
Indian Ocean?
How can a man be living in the Indian Ocean? No.
You said that is where you live.
No, I'm living in Lagos here.
You said as a marine engineer, you have parcelled his career and sent it to the Indian Ocean.
Oh God!
I have suffered!
God!
I finished my school...
Stand up, sir.
Stand up and explain yourself.
Oh God.
You finished what?
I passed out of school 15 years ago and came to Lagos.
I worked with Niger Dock...
As what?
... as an engineer and I was sent to Poland to study.
As soon as I came back, within two months, I was promoted to a manager.
I heard a voice saying, "Resign and serve me."
You heard a voice saying?
"Resign and serve me."
I left my job.
My colleagues were laughing but I said that it was God who called me.
I started suffering.
I started ministering after going to school.
Ministering as what?
I started a church.
But, right now, you said that you are the one that made him to resign as a lion and tiger from the Red Sea,
so that he can serve you.
Me? How can I make myself resign?
You said if just now.
Hell no.
I can't make myself to resign.
My course mates, where they are now, I can't compare myself with them.
My qualifications are even better than some of them but I can't compare myself with where they are today.
Even though I travelled to many countries, I can't compare myself with them.
Where they are today?
Some of them even give me money.
I have been in France, South Africa and Poland.
So, you are not doing anything with your certificate?
Nothing.
You also said that this woman is not your wife and you came alone.
No!
She is my wife.
You said you came alone.
No, we came together.
We both came here.
She also said that you always accused her of being the cause of the problems in the house.
Even before we came here this morning, there was a problem that nearly made me to leave her in the house.
The whole thing started since yesterday.
Sometimes, I just get provoked.
What were you accusing her of?
Just a minor issue.
OK, who is she to you now?
She's my wife.
You heard it all.
So, the confession you heard initially was not from your husband.
The Lord has delivered you and you are free.
Amen.
Thank you.
Thank You, Jesus!
My husband is delivered.
Thank You, Jesus.
I am delivered!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
After his deliverance at The SCOAN, Pastor Ernest Ekah has taken the Emmanuel TV team
to the site of his church, which the evil spirit said he had completely destroyed.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
Arriving at their destination the team disembarks from their vehicle.
They have arrived at the site of Pastor Ernest's ministry in Lagos.
A banner outside explains the various activities of the ministry and it's weekly services.
The inside of the church reveals a small hall with roughly 50 chairs inside.
There is a small pulpit on the front with the church logo.
Let's listen to Pastor Ernest explain the extent to which the evil spirit has destroyed his life and ministry.
My name is Rev. Ernest Davis Ekah.
The woman beside me here is my wife, Mrs Sibongile Davis Ekah.
I am the General Overseer of this ministry, Salvation Covenant Gospel Church.
I am here to explain how the evil spirit had really destroyed my life and career.
Presently, we have been asked to go from this place.
They took us to court who gave an order for us to leave at the end of last month.
There was a lawyer that was helping me but because I didn't have money to give him,
he didn't follow the cause up properly.
During that period, I called and begged him to do whatever he could for the landlord to help me
because I had nowhere to keep all these items.
Even myself, I didn't know where I would go if I had left here.
The lawyer told me he would tell them to give me 14 days because I could not afford the money.
I didn’t even have money to eat, talk less of paying for this place.
Because of that, they took us to court and it was ruled that we should move out.
I had been going from one pastor to another trying to seek for help.
There was a pastor I met who gave me N10,000.
I told him I was no looking for money for food but to get a place,
even if it meant I had to pack all my properties and keep them there.
He said he didn't have.
I came back that day so depressed.
As you can see this church, if you came here on a Sunday service, you would cry.
The evil spirit said it had swept everything away and sent it to the Indian Ocean.
I am the great lion.
I am the tiger...
Living where?
... from the deep sea of India.
He stays in that church.
He is a pastor.
Let him pastor.
He will pastor and eat the dust unless he accepts to come back to me and serve me.
He must serve me.
What have you done to his ministry, as a pastor?
Mnistry?
I swept everything, put it in a container and sent it to the ocean.
Where is the ocean?
Right where I come from.
Everything about him, I parcelled it and sent it to the ocean, the deep ocean of India where I come from.
He said that he had swept everything, parcelled it and send it to the Indian Ocean.
To compare that to what is happening to me;
if you came here on Sunday, people would stand outside and begin to laugh
because sometimes, the people here are not up to six or seven, or ten.
There was a service we had six, seven persons here.
They are just youths.
Some of them were students and not working.
I have suffered.
I would try everything I could but nothing would come out of it.
But I thank God that from the moment I was delivered, I have peace in my mind.
I want the man of God and Emmanuel TV to help me out of this situation.
Right now, the toilets that we normally use have been broken by the landlord.
There is nowhere for someone to go to the toilet.
Where I am supposed to use as an office is where we hide our things and cook.
As you can see, this is where I am supposed to have an office but we use here to cook
and to hide our possessions.
We are using the fridge here as a cupboard because it is not working.
We just kept it here as a cupboard where we put plates.
You can just imagine the suffering Pastor Ernest and his wife had been passing through,
to the point where broken fridge became a storage cupboard for their small assortment of a household
utensils and appliances.
The fridge is not working so we use it as a cupboard to put plates and other things
so that the place would not look dirty.
These are our bags and other properties which we keep up here, as you can see.
This is where Pastor Ernest and his wife are keeping their few earthly belongings they still own,
alongside two racks, where they keep their clothings.
This is the mat, foam and net which we normally used to sleep inside the church when the night came.
Just as the evil spirit that had previously possessed Pastor Ernest had confessed,
it has caused him poverty to the point where he and his wife were forced to sleep in their church,
due to their pitiable condition.
Bringing out an old mat and a piece of foam he moves into the church's centre to demonstrate
how the couple used to sleep every night.
This is where we used to sleep.
We would arrange it here, put four chairs and a mat on top.
I want to arrange it now.
Slowly laying out the mat on the hard floor, situated near to the pulpit where he would preach on Sunday,
Pastor Ernest proceeds to place four white plastic chairs at the edges of the mat.
He then unties and unrolls the old piece of foam and spreads it out on the mat.
The foam is worn out and is even falling apart due to its overuse.
The couple then drape a blue mosquito net on top of the four white chairs, to act as a cover
for a makeshift bed.
This is how we normally arranged the bed.
Then, we would enter inside and lie down.
The couple demonstrate how they would go to sleep every night.
You can just imagine the level the evil spirit had reduced this pastor to.
Truly, satan is a thief of our joy, comfort and dignity.
This is how we used to sleep because of the mosquitoes here.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
This was my experience.
This is how we had been sleeping and suffering.
If you look at my appearance, you would think that I have everything.
I just tried to console myself and my wife would encourage me.
If not so, I don't know…
I just thank God that He has delivered me and I am now normal.
People that see me outside there don't believe that I don't have money
and there is where I slept, but this has been my life for a very long time.
I want man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners to help me out.
I want to show you the toilet which the landlord broke
and where we normally bath outside, because the landlord wants me to leave.
Pastor Ernest leads the Emmanuel TV team outside the church premises.
Let's hear from him about the challenges they faced everyday.
This is where we normally bath in the night.
Very early in the morning, we would come out here and fetch water from well and bath here.
We would take water from the well here.
This old dilapidated well was a source of water Pastor Ernest and his wife were forced to use.
Because of their condition they had to bath with this murky water everyday.
We would wake up very early and bath here so that people would not see us.
That is all.
This is the toilet which we normally used.
The landlord has broken the place as my time has expired to stay here.
This is the place we normally used as a toilet but the landlord has broken it
because I was asked to move within 14 days.
The toilet is in a terrible state, after it had been broken down by the owner, in protest of Pastor's Ernest
inability to pay rent for the premises.
A small hole is all that remains amidst the debris.
If I am to leave here, there is nowhere to go because I don't have money to rent anywhere else.
That is why I am begging the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners to help me out.
Locking the gate of the church behind him, Pastor Ernest and his wife return to the vehicle
they have arrived in with the Emmanuel TV team.
One can just imagine what would be the fate of Pastor Ernest and his ministry if he had not come
to The SCOAN and received deliverance.
Given a notice to leave the premises immediately and with no money to move anywhere else
Pastor Ernest is pleading with Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners to support.
If not, he and his wife would be throst onto the streets.
My name is Rev. Ernest Davis Ekah.
Here beside me is my wife.
I studied Marine Mechanical Engineering in Poland.
I was working in a shipping company before I was sent to Poland to study for one and a half years.
We were 12 in number that were sent on that course.
When we came back, I was promoted to the office of a manager.
I was in that office.
After two months, there was a day during lunch period when I was in my office trying to study my Bible
and I heard a voice telling me, "I called you to serve me. Now, it is time. You have to leave your work to serve me".
I even discussed with some of my friends.
They said, "But you are the manager; everything is OK for you. How can you go and serve God?
To be a pastor, you are going to suffer".
I was struggling with those words.
After about two weeks, I forwarded my resignation letter.
When I left the work, I had to go to Bible College and I began to study.
After I graduated, I started a ministry.
Things were fine for the first four years.
What do you mean by "things were fine for four years", when you started?
The ministry was OK; a lot of miracles happened.
Everywhere was filled to the brim, even outside.
After four years, I had an encounter with a woman; we got married.
That was where my problem started.
When I saw that everything was upside down,
she sent me out of the house because we were living in her house.
She asked me to leave the house if I could not live by her rules.
I had no choice but to stay in the church.
I want to salute our woman here, that had been beside you.
What a wonderful woman - we salute you.
You know the reason why I said it.
Assume, it was this man alone facing all this, and there were no woman like this beside this man;
he would have committed suicide.
If I'm talking to you let me see your hand.
He would have committed suicide.
And two; if he had not committed suicide, he would have never thought of deliverance.
And I know his coming here is because of this woman.
Man of God, you are saying the right thing; I was about to commit suicide.
That fateful day, somebody came in and saw the rope I tied.
I was fed up with life because to live and eat was a problem for me.
I could be dressing like this – people did not know that these were all I had.
My wife did not know my predicament before we got married.
When I said that I lived in the church, she thought that in the church was a house,
a building where we would live like other churches have.
She did not know that it was right in the church after service we'd sleep.
My name is Mrs Sibongile Ernest Ekah
I come from Lesotho, South Africa.
Before I met my husband, I had been longing to come to The SCOAN.
One day, I met him on the internet and after some time, we got married.
He told me he was living in a church.
I came here.
When I came here, I was taking care of him because
I found that the life he was living was not something to write home about.
Since I have been with him, we have always been fighting.
He was wild, so I always begged him that we should come here.
At times, we would agree that we'd come but if we did not meet the man of God, he'd say,
"See, you said we should come here; I will not come here again".
Then, we would start quarrelling.
I thank God that today, he has received his deliverance.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
We want to salute you - thank you very much.
One thing we salute you for - you are the point God used to keep this man alive.
If not you, this man would be in his grave by now.
I know all the members will come together; I too want to join the family.
I want to join your family.
First, how you can leave that place and get your property -
at least a two bedroom apartment, settle down and we can pray with you.
We can pray with you and ask God the next line of action.
Sky will be your limit.
I want to join your family - thank you very much.
You help me to give them one million naira.
DEMON POSSESSED By A TIGER!!!
Mr & Mrs Ernest Davis Ekah Receiving One Million Naria And The Miror
Look. Amen. Sit down.
Educated South African Woman flying from South Africa and marrying a Nigerian, who is an engineer,
a manager in the company.
Herself is also a manager in the company in South Africa - they are coming together
and satan wants to ruin their lives just like that.
We should not allow that.
Look at the personalities involved.
Can you see - they are giving them bags of rice.
Now, you are to get them two bedroom flat today.
You know... when you leave here today - by tomorrow you will be able to get this two bed room flat,
or three bedroom flat.
Stand up!
OK, thank you.
Come on, madam!
Thank you very much.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
What God is using Pastor T.B. Joshua to do -
all of us sit here, watch and clap hands.
It is not enough.
He has done so much to touch the lives of everybody, including myself.
The church does not have any profitable venture; it is from this man, Pastor T.B. Joshua.
What he is doing, he is challenging us.
It is not enough to clap hands; we must start doing something.
He brings every Sunday no less than 10-20 million Naira.
Where is the money coming from?
So, today, I am going to give the couple five million Naira.
Thank you!
Member Of The SCOAN Writing A Cheque Of Five Million Naira For The Couple
And she is writing the cheque now.
She is writing a cheque; she wants to give 5 million Naira for the man.
Now! What else again?
So, you have money now to start something.
Thank you.
Go and give them.
Thank you very much.
OK, let's go together.
Member Of The SCOAN Giving A Cheque Of Five Million Naira To The Couple
I know some of you want still to come out.
You want to...?
Come, stand up here.
Call the pastor out.
When are you going to..., is it now?
Faith acts now!
Look, my brother is coming.
100 000 Naira – I will transfer it on my phone immediately.
You will transfer it on your phone?
Yes, on my phone – 100 000 Naira.
100 000? - now now now...
My brother.
Praise God!
Hallelujah!
I just came back from South Africa, yesterday.
By God's grace I will give him 500 000 Naira tomorrow morning.
500 000?
I will put it in his account.
Thank you very much - may God bless you.
I will give 200 000 Naira; I will get the account number now.
Thank you very much.
Wait for me, sir.
Go and wait for me.
TT ROBERT BEGIER